I mean, there is a single issue. The same reason we're devastating in trying to build a Gaza Lago in the Gaza Strip is the same reason why you can barely make rent.
It's why ICE is expanding to be a larger military force than the entire Marine Corps.
You know, it's there's only one issue. It's our entire political and economic system.
And, you know, I think it's Kwame Ture said, like, activists mobilize against issues. Revolutionaries organize against systems.
So one more time, say it one more time, say it one more time. Slow.
OK, activists mobilize for issues. Revolutionaries organize against systems.
So when Harris was on the campaign trail and we were criticizing her policies, people were like, you know, I'm sorry.
I can't afford to be a single issue voter. And I'm like, MF-er, there is only one issue.
It's all the same issue. I mean, I could write an entire dissertation connecting all these different issues, including the root.
Yeah.